Guide to the Mabou Mines Archive MSS.133
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII: Touring Files
  - Subseries A: Touring Files by Production
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Bardavon 1869 Opera House, Poughkeepse, NY (Box 41, Folder 1516)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Bardavon 1869 Opera House, Poughkeepse, NY lighting; see also OS for track sheets (Box 41, Folder 1517)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Hartford, CT see also OS for maps, etc (Box 41, Folder 1518)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Hartford, CT lighting; see also OS for plot (Box 41, Folder 1519)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Keane, NH (Box 41, Folder 1520)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Catamount, St. Johnsbury, VT (Box 41, Folder 1521)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Catamount, St. Johnsbury, VT lighting; see also OS for plot (Box 41, Folder 1522)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Univerisity of Massachusetts at Amherst (Box 41, Folder 1523)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Univerisity of Massachusetts at Amherst lighting; see also OS for plot (Box 41, Folder 1524)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Northeastern University, Boston, MA (Box 41, Folder 1525)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Northeastern University, Boston, MA lighting (Box 41, Folder 1526)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Dartmouth, Hanover, NH (Box 41, Folder 1527)
    - various productions 1986 financial records (Box 41, Folder 1528)
    - Cold Harbor 1986 tech specs (Box 41, Folder 1529)
    - Cold Harbor Spring 1986 tour itinerary, contracts, etc (Box 41, Folder 1530)
    - Cold Harbor Spring 1986 tour itinerary; includes flyers and Prelude… 8x10 print (Box 41, Folder 1531)
    - Cold Harbor Feb-Mar 1986; Atlanta, GA (Box 41, Folder 1532)
    - Cold Harbor Feb-Mar 1986; Atlanta, GA lighting; see also OS for plot (Box 41, Folder 1533)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 11, 1986; University of Vermont, Burlington (Box 41, Folder 1534)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 11, 1986; University of Vermont, Burlington lighting; see also OS for plot, track sheets (Box 41, Folder 1535)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 14, 1986; Williams College, Williamstown, MA (Box 41, Folder 1536)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 14, 1986; Williams College, Williamstown, MA lighting; see also OS for plot, track sheets (Box 41, Folder 1537)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 26-30, 1986; Charleston, SC (Box 41, Folder 1538)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 26-30, 1986; Charleston, SC lighting; see also OS for plot, track sheets (Box 41, Folder 1539)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine Sep 1986; Iowa City tech specs (Box 41, Folder 1540)
    - Cold Harbor [Sep] 1986; Kansas City, MO (Box 41, Folder 1541)
    - Cold Harbor Sep-Oct 1986; University of Iowa, Iowa City lighting (Box 41, Folder 1542)
    - Cold Harbor [Sep-Oct?] 1986; Southwest Missouri State University, Springfield, MO lighting; see also OS for plots, track sheets (Box 41, Folder 1543)
    - Company Oct 1986; Iowa City (Box 41, Folder 1544)
    - Cold Harbor Oct 7, 1986; University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign lighting; see also OS for plot, track sheets (Box 42, Folder 1545)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236029
    - Cold Harbor Nov-Dec 1986; UC Davis see also OS for plots, charts (Box 42, Folder 1546)
    - Cold Harbor Nov-Dec 1986; Humboldt State University, Arcata, CA see also OS for plots (Box 42, Folder 1547)
    - Cold Harbor 1987 tech specs (Box 42, Folder 1548)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine Apr 1987; Tallahassee, FL (Box 42, Folder 1549)
    - Cold Harbor May 1987; Valladolid, Spain (Box 42, Folder 1550)
    - Cold Harbor May 1987; Valladolid, Spain (Box 42, Folder 1551)
    - Cold Harbor May 1987; Valladolid, Spain sample press kit (Box 42, Folder 1552)
    - Cold Harbor May 1987; Valladolid, Spain see also OS (Box 42, Folder 1553)
    - Cold Harbor Aug 1987; Philadelphia (Box 42, Folder 1554)
    - Company Sep 22-25, 1987; University of Texas at Austin (Box 42, Folder 1555)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Sep 22, 1987; Ohio Wesleyan University (Box 42, Folder 1556)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Sep 25, 1987; Oberlin College, Ohio (Box 42, Folder 1557)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Oct 9-10, 1987; St. Louis, MO (Box 42, Folder 1558)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Oct 9-10, 1987; St. Louis, MO (Box 42, Folder 1559)
    - Cold Harbor 1988 film files (Box 42, Folder 1560)
    - Cold Harbor 1989 tech specs (freight) (Box 42, Folder 1561)
    - Help Wanted Jan 1989 (Box 42, Folder 1562)
    - Cold Harbor June 1989; District Curators, Washington, DC (Box 42, Folder 1563)
  - Subseries B: General Touring Files
    - touring correspondence, information, 1981-1985 (Box 42, Folder 1564)
    - touring pack, 1982-1983 (Box 42, Folder 1565)
    - international touring correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 42, Folder 1566)
    - tour information; publicity package, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 1567)
    - miscellaneous touring files, 1986-1989 (Box 42, Folder 1568)
    - national touring correspondence, information, 1986, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 1569)
    - touring correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 42, Folder 1570)
    - touring correspondence, 1990, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 1571)
    - international touring correspondence, information, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 1572)
    - correspondence, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 1573)
    - touring inquiries, contact information, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 1574)
    - touring inquiries, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 1575)
    - touring inquiries, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 1576)
    - general touring files - mailing schedules, administrative notes, presenting org. info, etc., 1991-1994 (Box 138, Folder 2043)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236227
    - correspondence, touring inquiries, 1991-1992 (Box 138, Folder 2044)
    - contact lists, 1991-1992 (Box 138, Folder 2045)
    - touring contact memos, 1992-1994 (Box 138, Folder 2046)
    - touring contact memos, undated [ca. 1992-1994] (Box 138, Folder 2047)
    - touring contact memos, undated [ca. 1992-1994] (Box 138, Folder 2048)
  - Subseries C: Travel Information
    - airline miles: Pan Am, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 1577)
    - airline miles: Delta, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 1578)
    - airline miles: American Airlines, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 1579)
    - airline miles: United Airlines, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 1580)
    - airline miles: Continental, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 1581)
    - travel discounts, undated (Box 42, Folder 1582)
    - Boston, Cambridge, undated (Box 42, Folder 1583)
    - Los Angeles, undated (Box 42, Folder 1584)
    - Montreal, Quebec, 1983-1984 (Box 42, Folder 1585)
    - Greece, undated (Box 42, Folder 1586)
  - Subseries D: Organizations and Festivals
    - Arizona Public Service Co., re: "WYIMA", 1994 (Box 43, Folder 1587)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236037
    - International Theatre Institute, 1984, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 1588)
    - Mid Atlantic States Arts Consortium, undated (Box 43, Folder 1589)
    - Sundance Institute, 1988, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1590)
    - Western Alliance of Arts Administrators, 1983, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 1591)
    - Yellow Springs Institute, 1987-1993 (Box 43, Folder 1592)
    - Autumn Festivals of Barcelona, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1593)
    - Belfast Festival at Queens, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1594)
    - Belluard-Bollwerk Festival Fribourg, 1988, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1595)
    - Blackpool Grand Theatre, 1989-1991 (Box 43, Folder 1596)
    - Brighton Festival '91, program, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1597)
    - Chianti World Festival of Contemporary Drama, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1598)
    - De Singel, Belgium, 1986-1987, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1599)
    - Dublin International Festival, undated (Box 43, Folder 1600)
    - du Maurier World Stage, Harbourfront, 1986-1987 (Box 43, Folder 1601)
    - Edinburgh International Festival, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1602)
    - Hamburg, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1603)
    - Hebbel Theatre, Berlin, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 1604)
    - Mayfest Limited, Scotland, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1605)
    - New York International Festival of the Arts, 1988, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1606)
    - Orlando International Fringe Festival, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 1607)
    - Riverside Studios, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1608)
    - Samuel Beckett Festival, The Hague, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 1609)
    - Shaw Theatre, London, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1610)
    - Sommerszene '90, catalogue, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 1611)
    - Tampere International Theatre Festival, Finland, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 1612)
    - Theaterburo Hannover, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1613)
    - Théâtre de la Bastille, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1614)
    - Tramway, Scotland, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1615)
    - Vancouver Fringe Festival, applications, 1992-1994 (Box 43, Folder 1616)
    - Wiener Fest Wochen, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1617)
    - European contacts, undated (Box 43, Folder 1618)
- Series IX: Video Recordings
  Video recordings of complete Mabou Mines productions, unless otherwise noted.
  - Subseries A: Video Recordings - Access Copies
    Subseries contains all researcher access copies of video material. Titles are arranged alphabetically.
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
    - AFI Video Festival: Dub of News Report, Undated (Case 133.0812)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      DVD
      Duration: 00:04:00
    - The B. Beaver Animation, June 1978 (Case 133.0384)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Duration: 00:19:58
    - The B. Beaver Animation, 1979 (Case 133.0387)
      Duration: 00:32:45
    - The B. Beaver Animation; Susan Stein Shiva Theater/Public Theater, June 4, 1990 (Case 133.0044)
      VHS
      Duration: unknown
    - The B. Beaver Animation Studio Version, undated (Case 133.0045)
    - The B. Beaver Animation, June 4, 1990 (Case 133.0046)
    - The B. Beaver Animation Excerpt, Undated (Case 133.0653)
      Duration: 00:10:00
    - The B. Beaver at The Public, Undated (Case 133.0656)
      Duration: 00:57:00
    - Bill [Raymond] Pho B&W Stills, Undated (Case 133.0659)
      Duration: 01:02:00
    - Boston Music Viva: New Works, Undated (Case 133.0854)
      Duration: 00:09:00
    - The Bribe; Ontological-Hysteric Theater, undated (Case 133.0011)
    - The Bribe; Ontological-Hysteric Theater, November 4, 1992 (Case 133.0012)
    - The Bribe; Arizona State University, February 1995 (Case 133.0016)
    - Cold Harbor; Primer Gran Festival/ Mexico City, Mexico, August 1989 (Case 133.0072)
    - Cold Harbor Promo Tape, Undated (Case 133.0686)
      Duration: 00:11:00
    - Cold Harbor Reel 1, Undated (Case 133.0680)
      Duration: 01:00:00
    - Cold Harbor Reel 2, Undated (Case 133.0683)
      Duration: 00:30:30
    - Dead End Kids 3/20/82 2nd Take, 1982 (Case 133.0821)
      Duration: 00:50:00
    - Dead End Kids: A Story of Nuclear Power, undated (Case 133.0236)
    - Dead End Kids Act II, Undated (Case 133.0824)
      Duration: 00:52:00
    - Dead End Kids, Mabou Mines/ Workprint New Improved Color Version, Undated (Case 133.0827)
      Duration: 00:37:00
    - Dead End Kids, Mabou Mines/ Workprint, undated (Case 133.0830)
      Duration: 00:36:00
    - Dead End Kids, Mabou Mines/ Film Workprint, Undated (Case 133.0833)
    - Dead End Kids/Franklin + Jefferson, Undated (Case 133.0836)
      Duration: 00:38:00
    - Dead End Kids: A History of Nuclear Power Workprint Part 1, undated (Case 133.0839)
      Duration: 00:53:00
    - Dead End Kids: A History of Nuclear Power Workprint Part II, undated (Case 133.0842)
    - Doris Chase Concepts Lies Mabou Mines, Undated (Case 133.0797)
      Duration: 00:30:00
    - Flow My Tears - Show Tape #1, 6/2/1988 (Case 133.0390)
      Duration: 00:25:30
    - Flow My Tears - Show Tape #2, 6/2/1988 (Case 133.0393)
      Duration: 00:11:27
    - Flow My Tears - Doc of Show #1, 7/7/1988 (Case 133.0396)
      Duration: 00:18:46
    - Flow My Tears - Doc of Show #2, 7/7/1988 (Case 133.0399)
      Duration: 00:53:17
    - Flow My Tears - Doc of Show #3, 7/7/1988 (Case 133.0402)
      Duration: 00:55:20
    - The Gospel At Colonus, undated (Case 133.0116)
    - The Gospel At Colonus, undated (Case 133.0117)
    - [1]-- The Gospel At Colonus, Inc. [2]-- The Quantum, undated (Case 133.0118)
    - Greg Mehrten, Undated (Case 133.0668)
      Duration: 00:54:30
    - Greg Mehrten pt. 2, Undated (Case 133.0671)
      Duration: 00:08:30
    - HAJJ (in performance)-Lee Breuer, May 8, 1986 1 of 1 (Case 133.0770)
      Duration: 00:54:00
    - HAJJ (in performance)-Lee Breuer, May 8, [1987] (Case 133.0767)
      Duration: 00:55:22
    - Hajj (Center Monitor)/, undated (Case 133.0205)
      15-minute production element
    - HAJJ Copy #1, Undated (Case 133.0806)
      Duration: 00:23:00
      This tape has severe image distortion.
    - HAJJ Master 2 Dissolve, undated (Case 133.0809)
      Duration: 00:14:00
    - HAJJ: NBC Master Tape, Undated (Case 133.0800)
    - HAJJ Outtake #1A, Undated (Case 133.0773)
    - HAJJ OUttake #1B, Undated (Case 133.0776)
      Duration: 00:28:00
    - HAJJ OUttakes #2, Undated (Case 133.0779)
      Duration: 00:51:00
    - HAJJ Outtakes #3A, Undated (Case 133.0782)
      Duration: 01:03:00
    - HAJJ Outtakes #3B, Undated (Case 133.0785)
      Duration: 00:31:00
    - HAJJ Outtakes #4A, Undated (Case 133.0788)
    - HAJJ Outtakes #4B, Undated (Case 133.0791)
    - HAJJ Outtakes #4C, Undated (Case 133.0794)
    - HAJJ: Written and Directed by Lee Breuer, Undated (Case 133.0803)
    - Idle Tears "Every Day", Undated (Case 133.0887)
      General Note
      Format: DVD
    - Imagination Dead Imagine (1984) (Case 133.0863)
      Duration: 00:17:45
    - "Imagination Dead Imagination", Undated (Case 133.0881)
      Duration: 00:07:00
    - "Imagination Dead Imagination" excerpts from the performance (Case 133.0878)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine, Mabou Mines: (1984) Master (Case 133.0851)
      Duration: 00:19:00
    - Imagination Dead Imagine; The Performing Garage, 1984 (Case 133.0250)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine- Interviews: Raw Footage 2/20/1986 (Case 133.0848)
      Duration: 00:22:00
    - Imagination Dead Imagine, undated (Case 133.0241)
    - It's A Man's World (Act I); Los Angeles Theatre Center, September 26, 1985 (Case 133.0265)
    - It's A Man's World (Act II); Los Angeles Theatre Center, September 26, 1985 (Case 133.0266)
    - Jungle Clip Reel, Undated (Case 133.0911)
      Duration: 00:22:30
    - Jungle 1st Hour IJC.002, Undated (Case 133.0905)
    - Jungle 2nd Hour, Undated (Case 133.0908)
    - Lee Breuer pt. II, Undated (Case 133.0662)
    - Lee Breuer pt. III, Undated (Case 133.0665)
    - Selections from Mabou Mines/Lee Breuer, Undated (Case 133.0743)
      Duration: 00:21:00
    - The Lost Ones; The Public Theater, March 1976 (Case 133.0112)
    - The Lost Ones 1976 (March) Public Theater (Case 133.0731)
    - The Lost Ones, undated (Case 133.0113)
    - The Lost Ones, Undated (Case 133.0734)
    - Mabou Mines Compilation 4/27/94 Master + Music Videos, 1994 (Case 133.0917)
      Duration: 00:42:00
    - Mabou Mines Development Foundation, undated (Case 133.0845)
      Duration: 00:15:00
    - Mabou Mines Dev., Undated (Case 133.0860)
      Duration: 00:08:00
    - Mabou Mines Hajj 1, Undated (Case 133.0815)
    - Mabou Mines IDI Videotape, Undated (Case 133.0872)
      Duration: 00:18:00
    - Mabou Mines: Imagination, undated (Case 133.0857)
    - Mabou Mines: Imagination Dead Imagine, Undated (Case 133.0869)
    - Mabou Mines: Imagination Dead Imagine, Undated (Case 133.0866)
      Duration: 00:20:00
    - Mabou Mines' Lear; Smith College, Tape 1(of 2). March 31, 1989 (Case 133.0144)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear; Smith College, Tape 2(of 2), March 31, 1989 (Case 133.0145)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear; Triplex Theater, NYC, Tape 1(of 2), January, 1990 (Case 133.0152)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear; Triplex Theater, NYC, Tape 2(of 2), January, 1990 (Case 133.0153)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear; Triplex Theater, NYC, Tape 1(of 2), January, 1990 (Case 133.0154)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear; Triplex Theater, NYC, Tape 2(of 2), January 1990 (Case 133.0155)
    - Mabou Mines Lear Performance 2/3/90 Triplex 1 of 3, 1990 (Case 133.0758)
      Duration: 00:59:00
    - Mabou Mines Lear Performance 2/3/90 Triplex 2 of 3, 1990 (Case 133.0761)
      Duration:01:02:00
    - Mabou Mines Lear Performance 2/3/90 Triplex 3 of 3, 1990 (Case 133.0764)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear, Tape 1(of 3), undated (Case 133.0170)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear, Tape 2(of 3), undated (Case 133.0171)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear, Tape 3(of 3), undated (Case 133.0172)
    - Mabou Mines Lear Work in Progress, Undated (Case 133.0746)
      Duration: 00:40:00
    - Mabou Mines Lear 2, Undated (Case 133.0749)
      Duration: 00:43:30
    - Mabou Mines Lear 3, Undated (Case 133.0755)
      Duration: 00:43:00
    - Mabou Mines Lear Reel 4, Undated (Case 133.0752)
    - Mabou Mines, Music Video, Undated (Case 133.0677)
      Duration:00:05:00
    - Mabou Mines Production of Imagination Dead Imagination, Undated (Case 133.0875)
    - Mabou Mines: The Saint and the Football Players on German TV, Undated (Case 133.0896)
      Duration: 00:07:30
    - Mother; La Mama, November 5, 1994 (Case 133.0297)
    - Inside of "Mother", undated (Case 133.0300)
    - Inside of "Mother", undated (Case 133.0304)
    - Parts 4 & 5 of "anna" Sequence from Far From Poland, Undated (Case 133.0920)
      Duration: 00:11:21
    - Prelude to Death in Venice, May 13, 1986 (Case 133.0701)
    - Prelude to Death in Venice, Undated (Case 133.0698)
    - 3/4" Prelude Sample Video (AFT Grant Film), Undated (Case 133.0704)
      Duration: 01.02.00
    - Prelude to Death in Venice, Part I of II, Undated (Case 133.0707)
      Duration: 00:13:00
    - Prelude to Death in Venice, Part II of II, Undated (Case 133.0710)
    - Prelude to Death in Venice, Dec. 26, Undated (Case 133.0716)
    - Prelude to Death in Venice, Dec. 26 w/Video FX, Undated (Case 133.0713)
    - Prelude to Death in Venice, a Work in Progress, Undated (Case 133.0719)
      Duration: 00:08:26
    - Part I and II, Prelude to Death in Venice, Undated (Case 133.0722)
    - Part II, Prelude to Death in Venice, Undated (Case 133.0725)
    - Prairie Dog Productions Trailers 2/24/84, 1984 (Case 133.0923)
    - Prelude to Death in Venice, PDV 4, Undated (Case 133.0728)
    - Pretty Boy Act III, Undated (Case 133.0692)
      Duration: 00:26:00
    - Pretty Boy, June 24, 1984 (Case 133.0079)
    - Pretty Boy Parts 1&2, Undated (Case 133.0689)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice (with Bill Raymond), undated (Case 133.0100)
    - A Prelude to Death In Venice (with Steve Peabody), 1992 (Case 133.0103)
    - The Red Horse Animation (Original Production), undated (Case 133.0121)
    - The Red Horse Animation, 1970 (Case 133.0122)
    - The Red Horse Animation, undated (Case 133.0123)
    - Reel to Real; Duke University, September 23, 1994 (Case 133.0275)
    - Ruth Malaczech, Undated (Case 133.0674)
    - The Saint and the Football Players (from German TV), 1979 (Case 133.0288)
    - The Saint and the Football Players (excerpts of 1983 production, 5 segments); Hippodrome State Theatre (Case 133.0291)
      Duration: 00:18:37
    - [1] The Sal Mineo Story [2] Pretty Boy: Cuts from Act II and III, Undated (Case 133.0695)
      Duration: 00:12:00
    - Sister Suzie, Undated (Case 133.0902)
    - Suenos; The Triplex Theatre, February 1989 (Case 133.0036)
    - Tape for Tokuma, ITVS, Undated (Case 133.0914)
    - Through the Leaves, Undated (Case 133.0884)
    - Through the Leaves; The Public Theatre, Tape 1 (of 2), 1990 (Case 133.0259)
    - Through the Leaves; The Public Theater, September 13, 1990 (Case 133.0260)
    - Two Head Video Production: Saint + The Football Players Opening Night, Undated (Case 133.0890)
    - Two Head Video: Saint + The Football Players Tuesday Night, Undated (Case 133.0893)
      Duration: 00:58:00
    - Video Festival Dub, Undated (Case 133.0818)
      Duration: 00:03:00
    - WNET/ Thirteen Gospel at Colonus Part I, Undated (Case 133.0737)
    - WNET/Thirteen Gospel at Colonus part 2, Undated (Case 133.0740)
    - The Warrior Ant, Part 1 and Part 2(puppet sequence); Alice Tully Hall/ Lincoln Center, June 16, 1986 (Case 133.0313)
      Duration: 00:18:35
    - The Warrior Ant, Acts 2 and 3; BAM Next Wave Festival, 1988 (Case 133.0318)
    - The Warrior Ant, undated (Case 133.0325)
    - The Warrior Ant, Undated (Case 133.0899)
  - Subseries B: Video Recordings - Originals
    Original video recording list is currently unavailable. Please check with Fales archivist for more information.
    - The Bribe, 1991; ID: 133.0001 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0001)
      VHS-C
    - The Bribe, 1991; ID: 133.0002 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0002)
    - The Bribe, 1991; ID: 133.0003 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0003)
    - Mabou Mines: The Bribe, 1991; ID: 133.0004 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0004)
    - Mabou Mines: The Bribe at P.S. 122, 1991; ID: 133.0005 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0005)
    - The Bribe at P.S. 122, [1991]; ID: 133.0006 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0006)
    - The Bribe, [1991]; ID: 133.0007 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0007)
    - The Bribe at The Ontological, 1992; ID: 133.0008 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0008)
    - The Bribe at The Ontological, 1992; ID: 133.0009 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0009)
    - The Bribe at The Ontological, 1992; ID: 133.0010 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0010)
    - The Bribe at the Singapore Arts Festival, 1994; ID: 133.0013 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0013)
    - The Bribe at The Singapore Festival of the Arts, 1994; ID: 133.0014 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0014)
    - The Bribe at The Singapore Festival of the Arts, 1994; ID: 133.0015 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0015)
    - The Bribe at ASU [Arizona State University], 1995; ID: 133.0017 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0017)
    - The Bribe at ASU [Arizona State University], 1995; ID: 133.0018 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0018)
    - The Bribe, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0019 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0019)
    - The Bribe, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0020 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0020)
    - The Bribe, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0021 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0021)
    - Selected Scenes from The Bribe, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0022 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0022)
    - Mabou Mines' The Bribe, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0023 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0023)
    - Mabou Mines' The Bribe, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0024 (Box 141, Media ID: 133.0024)
    - Sueños at P.S. 122, 1987; ID: 133.0025 (Box 142, Media ID: 133.0025)
      Betamax
    - Sueños Work Tape, 1988; ID: 133.0026 (Box 142, Media ID: 133.0026)
    - Sueños 1 - P.S.A. [Public Service Announcement], [n.d.]; ID: 133.0027 (Box 142, Media ID: 133.0027)
      3/4 in. Umatic
    - Sueños Dress #1, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0028 (Box 142, Media ID: 133.0028)
    - Sueños at Nu Arts, 1988; ID: 133.0029 (Box 142, Media ID: 133.0029)
    - Sueños, 1987; ID: 133.0030 (Box 142, Media ID: 133.0030)
    - Sueños at the Triplex, 1989; ID: 133.0031 (Box 142, Media ID: 133.0031)
      Betacam
    - Sueños at the Triplex, 1989; ID: 133.0032 (Box 142, Media ID: 133.0032)
    - Sueños at The Triplex, 1989; ID: 133.0033 (Box 142, Media ID: 133.0033)
    - Sueños at The Triplex [unedited], 1989; ID: 133.0034 (Box 142, Media ID: 133.0034)
    - Sueños at The Triplex, [1989]; ID: 133.0035 (Box 142, Media ID: 133.0035)
    - The B. Beaver Animation, Pt. 1; June 1978 (Continuity of Selected Takes without Post Production), ID: 133.0037A (Box 142, Media ID: 133.0037A)
    - The B. Beaver Animation, 1979; ID: 133.0038 (Box 142, Media ID: 133.0038)
    - The B. Beaver Animation Part II of 2, [1979]; ID: 133.0039A (Box 142, Media ID: 133.0039A)
    - B. Beaver (Fred), 1979; ID: 133.0040 (Box 142, Media ID: 133.0040)
    - B. Beaver Animation excerpt, [1979]; ID: 133.0041 (Box 142, Media ID: 133.0041)
      Existence and Location of Copies
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0653
    - B. Beaver (8 minute excerpt), [1979]; ID: 133.0042 (Box 142, Media ID: 133.0042)
    - B. Beaver at the Public, 1990; ID: 133.0043 (Box 142, Media ID: 133.0043)